

PROFILE

My name Farman Nadir Abdullah I'm 23 years old want to improve and develop my knowledge and skills as an active and hardworking employee.

After graduate in software and informatics Engineering Department at Salahuddin University.

I love working with people, specially if they have same passion I have .

INFO



1 Jun 1995



Single



Iraq/kurdistan



Erbil/Masif

CONTACT



farmannadir21@gmail.com



+964(750)-755-5967

LANGUAGE

ENGLISH

KURDISH

ARABIC

Farman Nadir

Software Engineer

Twitter:@FarmanNadir Facebook:Farman Nadir Instagram:Farman Nadir

COURSE TAKIN

- Mathematics I & Mathematics II
- Discreate Math & logic Design
- General English & java programming
- Scientific Database & Database & advance Database System
- Engineering analysis & Numerical analysis
- Operating System & Data Security & Computer Network

EDUCATION

2013-2014 • **Kurdistan High School** Erbil/30m

2017-2018 • Graduated from SUH-College of Erbil/Kirkuk Road Engineering - Software & Informatics Department

EXPERIENCE

2016-2017 • Mobile Application(Android):

> Developed an android application for kids to learning(letters, numbers, animals name and fruits name).

2016-2017 • **EIA(Erbil International Airport):**

Worked for summer training and got some basic experience

2016-2017 Volunteer at

Chro Project - TechEye

2017-2018 • **Engineering College**

- 1. Worked as a team a manager on SEDAF(Software Engineering Department Annual Fire)
- 2. Created and introduced a website for (Finding Nearest School in Your Location) for engineering college software and informatics department as a fourth year project.

- Microsoft Office (word Excel Access PowerPoint).
- Computer Languages (java java(GUI)).
- Database(Access MySQL MySQL I).
- Web Design(HTML CSS JavaScript and jQuery).
- Mobile Application (Android).
- Adobe photoshop.
- Having Experience in formatting a Computer.

Programming is My life